the Joe Rogan Experience.
>> When I was stationed at Portland Air
National Guard, my job there was an
airfield manager. So, I would interface
and work a lot with the F-15 pilots at
the unit. And so, um, there had been an
airspace incursion that had taken place
when I was still at the time at the
Guard. And I remember kind of talking to
some of the pilots about it and I was
like, "What was that?" And they're like,
"Eh, we can't really talk about it." And
no one really wanted to address it. And
so from what I had gathered, that had
been likely a UAP. Um, and so that kind
of was my perspective. Granted, I also
grew up in the generation of the X-Files
and you know, I don't know if you
remember 94 Independence Day. So like
for me specifically, I didn't look at it
with like a crazy lens and perspective.
I'm like, you know, you you never know
if you know, we're the only ones out
there essentially.
>> But why did you assume that if it's a
top secret incursion that he couldn't
talk about that it wasn't just a
military craft from another country?
because of the way that he was
discussing it.
>> How did he what did he say?
>> So, he had been um he didn't want to,
from what I gather, get taken off flight
status and he's like, I really can't
discuss it. Um we couldn't really like
identify it essentially and it had
outperformed them. And so that was my
first from a military perspective kind
of experience with someone who
basically, you know, there's a stigma
within the flight community. Um do you
want to lose your security clearance? um
what you know is there this level of
crazy that people kind of brand that
will stick with you and kind of ruin
your career
>> but doesn't he have instrumentation on
his jet
>> well at the time right so an older
platform but he really didn't want to
even talk about it and I bring that up
because now with our investigation and
the task force that I run actually the
reason why the task force was formed was
because of a event that happened at
Eglund Air Force Base where both myself
representative Matt Gates and
representative if Tim Burch actually had
responded and gone to investigate mult
multiple Air Force pilots that had come
forward in regards to UAP incidences
that had occurred and they were alleging
that the Air Force was covering it up.
>> Interesting.
>> Yeah. So that was that and like I'm
happy to go into detail on that one but
what I will tell you is the stuff that I
saw at Eglund how the military responded
me being you know a former service
member and then ultimately what I saw
with the the push back of the military
not even wanting to share with Congress
information which is a big problem
because when you have Congress that's
supposed to be the advocate and voice
for the American people the oversight
body and you're being denied access not
just from a base commander but high
level up at the Pentagon even secretary
of defense it's a problem. Do you think
that it's possible that these are US
vehicles that are top secret? I
definitely think that there's a level of
advanced technology that the US
government has and I think that that
that tech can be housed within the
defense contract realm and of course
some information is going to be
classified but I can also tell you and
this might sound crazy but based on our
investigations and stuff that we've seen
okay there is definitely something that
I think would rival what we know
currently with physics and a tech that
potentially is out there that we don't
have the ability to reproduce because it
would basically be like dropping a cell
phone cell phone right off back during
the time of maybe caveman. So like we
just don't have the tech to develop it
yet. What I can also tell you is based
on our interviews, and this has been
something that you can go back and watch
with the congressional hearings, but I
was actually able to ask some of the
witnesses, you know, what are these
things? And they keep saying
interdimensional. And then when you talk
about the interdimensional aspect of,
you know, are these things pre-existing
maybe outside of what we currently know
as our own dimension. Um, that stuff can
kind of all sound crazy, but at the end
of the day, you know, my job as an
investigator is to receive all the
information, decipher it, and then
ultimately from a congressional aspect,
if you do have contractors that are
withholding information or operating
outside of the purview of the federal
government, I mean, there's budgetary
issues, but there's definitely something
that I can tell you with confidence that
exists that we don't know how to explain
currently.
>> So, when you say that it operates
outside our understanding of physics,
what specifically are you saying? like
what what happened
>> to to I guess break it down in simple
terms is that I think that some of the
tech that exists that whatever these
things have these energy things have um
>> energy things well they call them inter
interdimensional beings I think that
they can actually operate through the
time spaces that we currently have and
that's not something that I came up with
on my own that's based on stuff that
we've seen that's based on information
that we've been told. And then also too,
I think that there's this historical
aspect of, you know, this gets into the
deeper theories and concepts of religion
and and I think the history that we
currently know and and that kind of
spins off into another topic of, you
know, you have the modern day Bible, you
have this aspect of Bibles that or books
of the Bible that have been removed that
explain and kind of touch on these
topics. And I think that we're in a time
and age where you have such a a vast
amount of information that we have
access to via social media, via your
cell phone, via the internet. And so
it's really changing the way that we
understand, you know, the origins of
life and and the spiritual reality that
we know.
>> When you say interdimensional beings,
that they know that these are
interdimensional beings. How do they
know that?
>> That so um based on testimony would be
based on witnesses that have come
forward. But what I can tell you,
>> so the witnesses just were told that
they were in that they've seen things
and what I can tell you without getting
into classified conversations um is that
there have been incidences that I
believe
where very credible people have reported
that there have been movement outside of
time and space.
>> That's very vague.
>> Yeah. So look,
>> unfortunately.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Look, um, have I seen a
portal open? No. Have I seen a spaceship
personally? No. Have I seen evidence of
this? Yes. Have I seen photo
documentation of aircraft that I believe
were not made by mankind? Yes. Is there
historical significance to this? Yes. Is
there multiple events that go back to, I
would argue, maybe even before the time
of Christ that have documented this in
text? Yes. So, do I believe that the
government has access to certain
technology? Yes, to an extent. And I
believe that certain contractors
potentially have backgineered this tech.
I think that that's what can explain the
advancements that we're seeing. But I
also believe that this is a dangerous
level of hidden information from the
American people because if you have an
aspect of the federal government, which
I can tell you I with two other members
of Congress were denied access to
information at Eglund Air Force Base
pertaining to whistleblowers because of
the fact and we can get into that story
and what happened at Eglund in a second,
but we were denied access and told that
we don't have security clearance or the
readin authority on a special access
program. That's a problem because I'm
supposed to represent and be an
investigative body and you have then
people who are unelected that are
operating basically in secrecy. Um and
and that's a problem. That's a big
problem.
>> And so how do these people have the
authority to do that?
>> I think it's been decades of classified
secret information then also this aspect
of the intelligence community that's
been empowered. And it's kind of
serendipitous with timing because when
you talk about the intelligence
communities and what they've done
essentially to the trust in this country
with the American people, I think this
goes all the way back even into JFK um
with how they basically have operated
outside of the purview of Congress and
and basically to an extent have gone
rogue up until recently. You're seeing a
big push and pull to try to reign in
these intelligence agencies currently.
>> Yeah. So what I want to bring it back to
evidence. You said that you've seen
evidence like what kind of evidence have
you seen?
>> I have seen photos. I have seen um
>> what have you seen photos of?
>> So, I was in a skiff and I can't discuss
all that was in a skiff, but what I can
tell you is based on the photos that
I've seen, I'm very confident that
there's things out there that have not
been created by mankind.
It seems crazy that people have access
to information that shows that there's
something outside of us that is more
intelligent, at least more capable than
we are, and they hide it from everybody
else. What I can tell you is that when
you have thousands upon thousands of
people around the planet throughout time
that have reported something,
>> right,
>> to say that those people are crazy, to
say that, you know, the whole concept of
even just asking the question that you
might not necessarily be psychologically
sound,
>> that in itself, you know, that's a
disinformation campaign to get people to
shut up about it. And that's that's a
problem. We know that the US government
has not exactly been clean and a lot of
what they've done with the American
people specifically to the topic of
UFOs. You have
>> which makes you think that it's probably
because there's something there. If you
think about the motivation they had with
Project Blue Book
>> when Jay Allen Heinik was running
Project Blue Book, this specific
intention was to discredit all stories.
>> And he ended up ultimately though after
all of his investigations becoming
someone that was like, I think those are
something cute. But that that's true.
Um, by the way, a lot of people might
not necessarily go on to Google and look
up that information, but you can
actually look up the declassified
reports from Project Blue Book. What's
also interesting though is when we're
talking about tech, right, the ability
for
this tech being that it exists to change
dependence for entire governments on
things like fossil fuel, etc. You know,
it's um, look, I think everyone has a
moral obligation to do what they think
is right. Okay? And so if you're in a
position of power and you see something
wrong and you're not addressing it, I
think you know this in itself getting
the truth out there for people to decide
for themselves. I'm not telling you what
to believe. I'm just telling you in our
investigations and what we are pushing
for in regards to transparency. I would
like to see the federal government roll
out some of the stuff that we've been
given access to because I think that
that information belongs in the hands of
the American people. And it's not even
just the US government. I mean there's
other countries around the world that
have done certain things like this. Now,
look, I've had a lot of crazy people
show up at my office and say, you know,
I like I've heard it all. Yeah. I've
been to Mars. Um, you know, I have a
chip in my brain, all this stuff.
>> They all have chips.
>> We had this one guy that showed up that
was like trying to give us a USB. He's
like, put this in your computer. They're
going to kill me for this. Like runs
away. And I'm like, I'm not putting that
in my computer. But based on our
investigations, what I will tell you is,
you know, there's been um two members of
Congress that are actually helping to
lead out these investigations with me.
And the reason I say that is because up
until last Congress, if you even said
the word UAP or UFO, people actually
told us that if we went forward with
these investigations that we were going
to ruin our political careers. And so,
you know, we're in the mindset of, well,
like why wouldn't we ask these
questions? And also too, if no one wants
to touch it, like there has to be
something here, right?
>> Right. And so in these investigations, I
mean, the amount of people that will
come up to us, very successful people to
multiple members of Congress that
believe the same thing, it's definitely
changed in regards to the stigma that
used to exist about disclosure and all
this. And so what we're trying to do
currently was there's a big documentary
that was filmed about a year and a half
ago and we're trying to get a screening
up on Capitol Hill. But look, I I think
a lot of people say, "Well, this is a
distraction from everything else
happening in the country right now." And
all I'm simply trying to say is it's not
a distraction. the people that are kind
of helping to divulge all this
information. You have an intelligence
community, you know, Tulsi Gabbard,
Radcliffe, Cash Patel, they they have
been truly in regards to our other
investigations extremely transparent and
wanting to get this information out. But
it doesn't mean that within these
intelligence communities, there isn't
push back. And so part of the reason why
the task force was formed pertaining to
things like UAP, pertaining to things
like the Jeffrey Epstein stuff,
pertaining to things like um the JFK,
MLK and RFK investigations is because
even though we don't hold
declassification authority, what we're
trying to do is push these agencies and
be, if you will, the pit bull and the
attack dog on trying to get this
information released. And to a lot of
these agencies credits, they've been
extremely transparent and we have gotten
wins specifically on the JFK stuff and
we're still looking to declassify and
ask specifically on the UAP topic. What
would be the rationale for keeping a
photograph of a known ab absolute not of
this world craft from the American
people or from the world? Why why would
anybody think that that would be the
smart thing to do is to limit the access
of that information to a very small
amount of people?
>> I think that part of the fear is is that
you have advisers that think that you
know um the American people or humanity
might not be able to handle it quite
there's this like protective complex.
But then also too, I think when you are
talking about these things
for a lot of people, I think that it
kind of can rock your world a little bit
in regards to where you stand in a faith
perspective and then also too um an
aspect of well, how do you even begin to
explain it? And all I'm going to say is
look, um, and we can go into some of the
books that were removed from what we
know as the modern day Bible, but I read
through the book of Enoch multiple
times. And I'm not saying that these
things are angels. Okay? That's that's
not at all what I'm saying. But what I
am saying is that
depending on where you are in regards to
your whole perspective on whether or not
God exists, like I believe in God, I'm a
Christian. Um, there has to have been
and there's admissions that there was
other
creations that God made, but that we
were the most prized creation. And so I
think that this can open up a bigger
topic of discussion.